# LAURA SHY

## CONTACT

■ Ishybrohm@gmail.com

540 - 755 - 9885

in /laura-shy

#### WORK SKILLS

HTML Express CSS REST

JavaScript PostgreSQL Node.js MongoDB

**REACT** 

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Interpersonal Skills
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

#### TOOLS

Microsoft Word
Microsoft PowerPoint
Google Drawings
Google Sheets
Google Slides and Docs
Slack
Figma
Canva
MAC & PC Systems

Android & iOS Systems

#### ABOUT

Full stack web developer with a strong background in project management and managing multiple concurrent tasks. Former orchestra director experienced in analyzing a team to assess progress, procedures, and viable improvements to meet goals and ensure success.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Website for Thrive Music Academy

AUG 2021

- Guided the client through establishing a solid foundation for needs and wants of their website and business
- Created a single-page website for a new business in the community
- Produced flyers, logos, infographics, and a brochure for the client to better promote the business

#### Orchestra Director, HCPS and FCPS JUN 2016 - AUG 2021

- Ran the orchestral programs for middle schools and high schools in Virginia, educating and directing students in grades 6-12.
- Taught multiple levels of piano and music in special education.
- Maintained instrument inventories, music libraries, attire inventories, and finances for all orchestra programs.
- Planned and executed fundraisers, concerts, events both local and long-distance, and small to large scale trips.
- Designed attire and marketing tools for the programs.
- Taught students both virtual and in-person simultaneously, and created digital content and concerts during the 2020-2021 year.
- Proficient in Microsoft and Google suites

#### EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB
DEVELOPER PROGRAM

CareerFoundry Jan 2021 - Nov 2021 BACHELOR OF ARTS, MUSIC EDUCATION

Crane School of Music, SUNY Potsdam 2011 - 2015